# Soyab Mostofa

Working as a manager at my own startup with my partners. My responsibilities include identifying potential clients, understanding their gap, pursuing to fulfil their needs as well as administrative and planning duties.

I possess excellent computer expertise as well as communication skills. Highly focused, able to lead and work for a team as demonstrated throughout my academic and entrepreneurial career. Have both academic and practical expertise in Marketing, Campaign planning, Data analysis and Freelancing. My Research Interest lies on Consumer behavioural psychology and Its Effects, Management Information System, Statistical data Analysis and Machine learning.

## **Permanent Residence:**

21/10 Pallabi, Mirpur 12, Dhaka 1216 Cell Phone: +880 186 504 8207

#### **Contact information**

Email: soyabmostofa@gmail.com

Linkedin: in/soyabmostofa

Github: soyab-mostofa

Skype: live:soyabmostofa

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Clyde Visuals - Chief technical officer

FEB 2022 - PRESENT

- Planned sustainable growth plan and blue ocean marketing strategy.
- Educate clients about 3D real estate visualisation marketing
- Made cost to profit maximisation structure.
- Visit potential sites and make virtual 360 tours.

#### Woodmaxdecor – Manager

AUGUST 2021 - Present

- Promote Business through digital platforms. (With banner/ ads/word of mouth)
- Research market trends for potential clients.
- Do market surveys for clients and suppliers.
- Design interior/ furniture for shops and home (4 locations)
- Make B2B communication efficient and streamlining the delivery process to customers.
- Quality control and management through customer feedback.

## Hexatech Solutions - Full-stack web developer

FEB 2021 - MAY 2021

- Make JamStack webapps
- Design UI/UX for clients
- Identify Brand image and colour scheme.
- Meeting with clients for Efficient product placement on the web.

## Furniturewala - Administrative manager

SEP 2020 - FEB 2021

- Manage employees and product orders so all goes according to deadline.
- Design UI/UX for clients
- Identify Brand image and colour scheme.
- Meeting with clients for Efficient product placement on the web

#### **Extra-Curricular Activities**

Business competitions:

- Second rounder in Admaker bangladesh 2019
- First rounder in Brand drill by DU Marketing club
- Second rounder in champions of the earth (sustainable rice husk idea)

## The Marketing Club:

Designation: Senior member

- Strategic planning and research activities to plan new events.
- Plan and coordinate the biggest marketing club event in NSU ELEMENTUM
- Travelled to different locations in order to promote the club's events and sponsorship.
- Was part of the management team in three events with more than fifteen hundred participants.
- Generated ideas for hosting the upcoming events.
- Volunteered to maintain participants and guests for the competition.

## Other ECA for NSU Student affairs:

- Volunteer for CPC Career Fair | North South University
- Visit to Coca cola factory and see the manufacturing and management process
- Promote Only University run tv broadcast in bangladesh NSUTV and Radio
- Head of IT for NSU's only live talk show program NSU TALKS, During quarantine.

#### **Computer Skills**

- Microsoft Office
- Adobe Illustrator / Premiere Pro
- Packages,
- SketchUP,
- JavaScript,
- NodeJS
- Python
- Linux

## **Special Interests**

- Project planning and implementation
- Web Development
- Machine Learning
- Study Neurology
- Read Books (Fiction/ nonfiction)
- Data analysis
- Presenting new Ideas

**Language Proficiency:** Bangla (Native), English (Full Professional Proficiency)

#### **EDUCATION**

# North South University — Bachelor of Business Administration

SEP 2017 - Expected 2022

CGPA: 3.01 (With scholarship)

**Major Courses:** Consumer Behaviour, Strategic Marketing, Digital marketing, Business Communication, Financial and Managerial Accounting, Finance, Marketing, Human Resource management, Entrepreneurship

# Government Laboratory high School and Collage- Science

2004-2016

SSC Result: 4.36 HSC Result: 4.00

#### References

#### Md Mahmudul Hasan

Head of SME,

Banglalink Digital Communications Ltd.

Cell: 01911310870

Email: mhasan.iub@gmail.com

# Irfan UL Hoque

Executive Director,

Fatullah Group

& Director of Hexatech solutions

Cell: 01701220702

Email: irfan.hexatech@gmail.com